Guide to the Stanford University Audio Collection SC1074 SC1074
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Audio recordings
  - Spouse Quarter Lecture Series
    - 1973 Oct 9, 15_07; 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 15)
    - 1973 Oct 16, 15_08; 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 15)
    - 1973 Oct 23, 15_09; 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 15)
    - Lepper, Mark, 1973 Oct 30; 15_10; 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 15)
    - 1973 Nov 13, 15_11; 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 15)
    - Stanford Alumni Association, 1974 Feb 12; 15_12; 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 15)
    - Jim March, Leadership and Success, 1974 Feb 19; 15_13; 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 15)
    - Tma #270 Stanford Alumni Association, 2PM Remson Barchas, 1974 May 17; 15_14; 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 15)
  - Plaque ceremony, 2005 Jun 11; 1 optical disc(s) (cd-r) (Box 15)
  - Plaque ceremony, 2006 Jun 17; 1 optical disc(s) (cd-r) (Box 15)
  - Snapshots: Stanford Soundtrack Volume Four, 2005; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 15)
  - Engelbart, Doug, Tymshare, Inc.: Facilitating High Performance Among Knowledge Workers, 1982; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 15)
  - Card, Stuart: The Psychology of Human - Computer Interaction, 1982; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 15)
  - Stark, Lawrence, U. C. Berkeley: Visual Fatigue, 1982; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 15)
  - Vendor Panel: Kevin Considine, Tektronix; Lee Falco, Falco Data Products; Tom Bentley, Hewlett-Packard, 1982; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 15)
  - Smith, Michael, NIOSH: Health Issues in VDT Use, 1982; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 15)
  - Keen, Peter, M.I.T.: Information Systems and Organizational Change, 1982; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 15)
  - McPheron, William - "Spirit of Saronyan" KQED, 1997 May 09; 16_1 (Box 16)
  - Lexicography and Language in the Digital Age -Tape 1 of 2, 2000 Apr 20; 16_2 (Box 16)
    Introduction Remarks Michael A. Keller Anna Morpurgo John Simpson Beth Levin Chris Manning
  - Lexicography and Language in the Digital Age -Tape 2 of 2, 2000 Apr 20; 16_3 (Box 16)
    Question and Answer Session
  - William McPheron - "Spirit of Saroyan" - Panel Tape 1, 1997 May 10; 16_4 (Box 16)
  - William McPheron - "Spirit of Saroyan" - Panel Tape 2, 1997 May 10; 16_5 (Box 16)
  - KZSU Sports/90.1 FM: Cardinal Baseball/A Champion Season, Narrated by David Fisher, 16_6 (Box 16)
  - Ettlinger talk on Nuremberg Chronicle, 16_7 (Box 16)
  - Pres. Sterling, Bay Area Alumni Clubs meeting (retirement dinner), 1968-03-05; 17_01; 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 17)
  - Skit night, Bob Bush, A. Doty, MacOsbourne (Napier, Schmidt, Maccoby sing), 1967; 17_02; 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 17)
  - Committee on Land and Building Development Hearing on the Proposed Stanford, 17_03; 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 17)
  - Faculty Club Show, 1968-04-13; 18_04; 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 18)
  - University Land Use Policy/Plan (Livingston Blayney Report), 1971-04-19; 17_04; 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 17)
  - Associated Students of Stanford University Axe Commission present the 24th Annual Spring Sing: A Journey into Spring., 1965; 16_1; 1 audio disc(s) (Box 19)
  - Turner, Joseph R., III, 19_4:6; 3 audio disc(s) (Box 19)
    KSU transcription disc
  - The Stanford University Choir, Motets, 19_2; 1 audio disc(s) (Box 19)
    MLR 5001
  - The Stanford University Chorus and The Stanford University Symphony, Excerpts from The Mass in B Minor by Bach, Johann Sebastian, 19_3; 1 audio disc(s) (Box 19)
  - April 3 Movement meeting, Tresidder Union (includes Bruce Franklin), 1969-05-21; 17_05; 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 17)
    Franklin, H. Bruce (Howard Bruce)
  - April 3 Coalition (9:20 to 10:40 pm), 1969-04-29; 17_06; 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 17)
  - Committee on Land and Building Development, Mr. Larry Livingston of Livingston and Blayney, 1971-03-30; 17_07; 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 17)
  - Faculty skit night, 1965-03-27; 17_08; 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 17)
  - Student Rally in Dinkelspiel Auditorium and White Plaza (from start of rally to departure for Computation Center sit-in), 1971-02-09; 17_09; 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 17)
  - Event at Cubberley, 1969-05-01; 17_1; 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 17)
  - U. N. Conference, Dinkelspiel Auditorium [partially damaged according to note inside], 1971-01-11; 17_11; 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 17)
  - SJC hearing, Jan. 29, 1971; Panel Discussion of KZSU; Rally before Trustee confrontation at GSB, 1971-0-29-1971-02-08; 17_12; 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 17)
  - KZSU, April 3 Movement, 1969-05-01; 17_13; 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 17)
  - SJC hearing, 1971-02-09; 17_14; 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 17)
  - Anti-War Rally, Old Union courtyard, 1971-02-10; 18_01; 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 18)
  - Alumni dinner honoring Dr. and Mrs. Sterling; John Dodds narration of slide show, 1968-03-05; 18_02; 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 18)
  - Faculty Dance Show: "My Fair Sponsor", "ProfessorBound", and "F.U.P.A. Fight Song" [typescript in box], 1966; 18_03; 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 18)